The voice is collide, the storm and the flame, laughter and chaos, it's part of the game.
Secrets unravel, the stage is alive, in Psyche's arena, the strange will survive.
Who's afraid?
Let it break from shadows to starlight
The truth will be shown
The psyche awakens
You're never alone
Expect the unexpected
Strange and unusual
Step inside the flow
The circus of shadows
It's Psyche's show
Terrible trolls in the dark
Take their stand
But angels are dancing
psyche's show
You can just imagine how dumb that person sounds.
It's like, I think I stopped saying whatever when I was like ten years old or something.
I bet we have a grown man here saying whatever, whatever mom, whatever mom.
Dork.
No way.
Like it, charisma?
Thank you.
Let's go guys.
Hey, good day, good day.
I did a little bit of...
I don't like the word tweaking anymore.
Should I say twerking?
Twerking of the mods?
I don't know.
I don't like the twerking of the mods.
Okay, I am modding some people.
But you know what?
It's fine.
Like really like loyal monty. I don't want these especially like
The people that are like, you know, I can't I can't have all these trolls as mods
I would love to you guys, but it's just like I just have to have the trolls as
Viewers you can't I can't I can't handle it. How are you guys KZ? What's up?
Yeah
I get in different, like, I get kind of moody.
Is that you, KZ?
Look at, look at, oh, look at this bigger whole thing.
Look at you.
That's what you look like?
Come on camera someday.
I know, and it's like, some of these people
I've still never met, hey, little tree frog.
I mean, if you wanna come on the panel,
at least get a, get a, you know,
see that avatar that KZ has?
I like that.
That's what you look like?
Okay
You've been on cam okay, I know but I'm very often and it's and Kate also
Come on guys if you want to be on the show all the time get a good microphone. I can't have
It's not the burping mics. I don't like the burping mics
But you know we'll work on it guys if I have to look on a rob racks. Well, what why can't you come up here?
What's the special on Rob racks?
I don't even know who the hell that is, but you don't come up here, but yeah, I think I got this though.
Now I can actually do some cool stuff. Do you like my new camera, by the way?
I think the camera looks better. This is not the last camera I had, not yesterday,
Time is he there? Is he there? And yeah, hold on. I'm gonna I will
I just want to say time
Do you want to be a mod or not like a like I so much to people I should ask like and
Okay, you think you fix the iphone setting, okay, I
Don't know Emma is yes, you do Casey. I've explained it to you Emma is this I don't have a picture handy, but
I'm not allowed to say her name, apparently.
She's a streamer.
She's a terror reader.
Okay.
Yeah, time, I know you got my back, so.
But I know I've been going back and forth with it,
it's like, keep,
I just wanna make sure I have people that want to.
Also, I don't know if you're on my Discord,
I wanna make sure
If you have Discord, the mods do go to my Discord
because I'm trying to kind of start that back up
and then have like a mod.
I wanna have a mod pow wow.
I really need to have one,
because I'm just thinking a lot about stuff, you know?
I wanna make sure we're all going in the same direction.
Okay, so one second.
80 members of my Discord.
Guys, there's been 80 members of my Discord.
There's not been a post there since March.
Marsh? Hold on. Am I seeing things?
Oh no, it's March 31st.
There hasn't been a post in five months. Is there? I don't know. What's going on?
Oh, hold on. That's a mod. It's a mod text. Okay, May text. Oh. Oh my gosh. Ew.
Oh my god.
Look at this.
Okay, that dork.
This was posted.
August 22nd today. That's him. Oh
That's AMC guys, that's like that. Oh god
I know who's gonna look like that
Hi, Loki hold on look Loki. I'm sorry. Okay, so yeah, you're
Loki would you like to be a model?
Okay
Look at the hairline, oh
We get a pat come on
That's J dogs, but buddy tone. Oh, it's J dog. Oh my god
So this is the guy that guys is the guy that struck the channel and he says the server is now
Property of him. Oh really. Oh
Really? Oh really Tony Bologna. I got you. I got you
Tony Bologna
That's his new name Tony Bologna
What's with gay guy in airlines? Yeah, this is your pilot speaking you are now evicted from the plane
But don't let the yeah door hit you on the way out. Okay. Yeah, it's Tony. Look. He's like
He's I think he looks weird. Oh, I
Didn't think he'd be like
It's kind of scary. I mean, it's like he posted this on my public. This is my server. So it's yeah, oh, and it's like I
Can't even do it. It's like
It's like his top teeth are like on
His lip and it's like it looks like he's he's kind of constipated. Hey, nobody nobody
Are you interested in being a mod or not? Like I just want to make sure and like everybody
I feel like I just modded people without asking last time,
and I just want to make sure,
I think we're on the same page with this.
You can like trains.
That's pretty dorky.
I don't know, that'd be, I mean,
it's like little train sets,
like it's like a,
I mean it's like, it was one thing,
like when you're an adult,
hey Nancy, how are you doing sweetie?
When you're an adult,
I guess like a train set is like,
Or he had a train said it's kind of cool, but adult I'd rather be like actually work on a track
Like you know, oh be on a real train not like I
Do like, um, you know, I do enjoy
You know some dolls Tony the conductor. Yeah, well
And guys he's I mean he seems kind of what's what's wrong with him like
Okay, what happened? Let's transpired. Okay. Okay. Well, yeah, okay, so I'm yeah
I really don't need very many mods. I just I need to have just like a
Good select. I think no one's gonna bother you. I don't think like people
I'm having a lot of people jump ship and stuff vacuum stream
I
Don't know. I don't really need to it's like I mean, it's like not terrible. I do have a couple of acu. So I actually I fixed my last
Vacuum that wasn't working and I have a new vacuum on team. It's like a new vacuum is not a pretty good one, but I
Had a choice I can I was like I can buy a
New vacuum or I can get a
VR headset
But I have to I have two vacuums in there fine. Okay, the two vacuums are fine really
The one I got on team you was like 20 bucks and it's like
Okay, but the other one I got working and so it's fine.
Yeah, I'm like not really gonna be offended
unless, you know, Gotti's not banned.
Guys, you know, I have like, you know,
sometimes it's my time of the month, you know,
which is like every day, right?
I don't know, it's my time of the day,
times, I don't know, it's like,
as they don't, if I'm like a little bit,
if I start getting bitchy, like,
It's best not to be even like addressed
Because I give I don't know I
I will like it. I get irritated
Okay, but yeah, and if and if you are not a mod it's my it was no it was last it was last night
It was my time of the day
Because I started like getting very irritated and then I I don't know but I
Usually get over it
Okay, J-Dog is on it. You don't you don't go over there and play with trains and stuff. Hey to the stage. How are you?
Let's see you get to see you
It's I go back and forth it's like I go back and forth between oh my god, they're trying to destroy my show to like
You know
It's okay. It's okay guys. I just I need like I think mainly I want like I won't move mostly female mods, too
I think his it's like
Where's the link?
Yeah, you can help up
But yeah, don't be offended about
wrenches, I think wrenches are just like
Like really it's like
It's more responsibility that you can be freer in the chat as long as yeah, I'll keep an eye on things
Yeah, you know I love Bita and it's like I can't I really can't have people
calling her names anymore it's like because I give it's like it would just
be as bad as if I did it basically because now it's like I'm really in
charge of the show okay I'm cooking lunch oh you have a date tonight oh great
Nancy how I'll be up in front of your date yeah so that's why your mic not
Honestly, there's
Very inexpensive microphones. I'm doing okay. I'm pretty good. Let me see a band loser for telling the guy that died name what?
I did I don't think I don't think that was the reason that he said King Cobra passed away
Okay, hold on. Who's this Dennis Robman? Let me see you on camera. Who's that? Oh, okay?
Yo, what's up psyche? Oh, yo, yo
What up guys dog like psyche give up moment it is a Keen Cobra's name Johnny Boston. Let's like say
Uh, you know rest in peace King Cobra. I saw his dad's post. Oh
Like he I like he some somebody was trying to get him on the show at one point. I was bitchy. It's okay
I you were all bitchy. Who are you talking about?
Accor tell
It's like yeah, I want to get rid of something bro. I'm not trying to cause no drama and I'm bro
Bro, they're lying. They're spreading narratives about me dude. I don't even know Tony the conductor
They're trying to stay on friends with him. The grease he uses to camey the conductor, bro
They use him to try to go after you they use him to try to be friends with you in the beginning
Well, I try to get access to you and now they're trying to say I'm friends with him you these people
They're playing Black Archie, Art Vandalay, Fifth Sage, Time, all these people are part of the
grease. These are all trolls. They're all part of that same little group. What did they want out
of, what did they want from me though? Like, I don't understand. They're trying to make you their
locale. So that way they're trying to run your channel, trying to tell you who and not to have
Someone that looks like that is trying to make me there. Look this guy. What he looks like. Yeah, I know I know I know I know that
I know much stupider than I could ever look. I
Know I know he's a joke. He's a joke. I know I get this but these guys are just trying to get you to kick off and
Just so they could try to run you same thing like they try to do with groovy Jimmy
That's why black RG so angry Jimmy because he got played by groovy Jimmy groovy Jimmy
I played him for money and tossed him aside because he knew what RG was about and that's why RG is so angry at groovy Jimmy
And he's angry at me because I'm friends with a lot of people that he they just don't want me around any of the communities
That's why they're trying to disdain my name trying to say I'm bad
Tony the conductor it's part of the same guy black RG
Guys guys from now on please don't call him Tony the conductor call him Tony below me. Okay, that's I don't know
Okay, Tony Baloney
Yeah
Same crew of people they're all part of the same crew people. They're just all trolls psyche
Yeah, but it's like I mean it's like there's a lot of trolls here and it's like and you know what is it?
Yeah, but these trolls are destructive these these trolls are ones they want to drive away people they're trying to they try to drive me away
They're trying to drive KZ away just just because they don't like people they try to manipulate the channel to only let you have
who they like on, who they want in the chat, just because they don't like them.
They can go away then. I mean, it's like if I have to, I'll just, I'll cancel my stream yard,
I'll get a, I'll get a subscription to stream elements or stream labs, and then I'll just,
I'll just just stream labs and then they're kind of ruin it for everybody, right? They have yeah
Yeah, but that's what that's what that's their goal psyche. They don't care
They want to ruin it. They want to ruin it. Yeah, they don't they don't care
Yeah
Guys, guys, you want me to go bother you?
You want me to go bother your channel?
They don't, they don't.
I'm talking about, I'll go bother your channels, though.
I will start going to your channels.
Thank you, but, but, but they don't, but here's the thing,
psyche, they don't care.
Their channels have been taken down.
I'm not scared of them.
Their channel, I know.
Yeah, they took in a groupie, Jimmy took their channels down,
but they create another one.
They don't care if their channels get taken down.
They're not on here for that.
They're on here just to create destruction and chaos.
So that's the only thing i'm here to tell you is that just watch out for them man just be careful man with these guys
I mean i've been much i mean i've been my channel's been
My channel's never been taken i mean it's been like i one time there
I took a little a little break for
But my channel's never been don't provoke them though. You know what?
You see they're threatening you they're threatening you that's what they're doing
If I show fear if I show fear then it's like they're like, oh, that's control. Okay. So yeah, and that's what they want
That's what they get to beat up. That's what they get to be this channel
No, that's exactly what they do a beat us. You got beat his channel taken down sick. No, no, no
I'm saying that they bullied her that's why black or G's a modda for beta and that's why I'm beat them
It backs him up even though. He's the one who docks her he did a whole live on her
He docks emperors Janet her family
You guys you know all three of us but my ally docks all three of us at once now. Yeah, I know that yeah
So I was like, I was docked too, but with Bita and Janon, so it's not like, oh, I understand, like, I know that they did that. Okay.
Yeah, yeah, but Bita's cool with these people and vouchers for these people and says, give these people wrenches when these people are trolls because Bita's scared of them.
Like, dude, this is ridiculous, man. This is like, Bita can't be scared of them because...
She is that's why she modded that that's why she modded black or she modded that's why she modded the king of the grease
The cream she modded he does not modded. Yes. She is I guarantee you I guarantee you
She likes them. I think she must like him or something. I don't think she would
He's charming. He's charming. Yeah, he's charming. I mean I had him like RG
He doesn't even care. I like RG too
But I can tell like, you know, last night last night last night last night RG and and Jamie Rose were on and they started
They started glazing
Bronzeberg and so I ended the show because it's like don't please I like bronze bird, too
Yeah, I don't like I don't like it. I don't like it, but I haven't you want me to pick you up with these people
by the way, so
If you want to say something I haven't seen them do anything to treat me with disrespect
Right
You're not a threat to them scum you're not a threat to them that's why you're not nothing to them
You haven't crossed their hairs you if you fuck with them or if you go anywhere near them and like talk shit to them
They will fuck with you. They will
Yeah, I never even I never they came here first and like yeah, I mean, but they don't really fuck with me
I don't think I mean I haven't had any
I know our family is porn bombed several times, but we're trying to yeah
That's what they do. They do it. They just like to destruct. They're just destructive people
I don't know why people put up with them. I
Well, I mean, I'm not going to I mean, it's like if you I mean guys, I'll have people. I mean, I'm just gonna have my mods
Keep an eye like close eye. Yeah. Yeah, just keep a eye on everybody. That's all. It's like it's like because I really don't see like I
mean
Like specifically, I know people will like, you know, kind of like I'm having the rules more enforced
But Joe hard did did you turn?
You against me a lot who said that huh?
Okay, Joe hard. Did they try to turn you against me? I want you to know this Joe hard. This is Joe hard
I don't know who the hell that is. I lose my mind probably six times a day. So don't uh, you know
You guys, you have your problems online.
I have my problems online and offline,
so what's crazy is you're caring about groups of people
that you can-
I'm not, I'm not caring, I'm just asking,
but hey, Scum, who's Johnny Boston?
Is that Kinkover or no?
No.
Who is it?
And explain it.
Oh yeah, you brought up the other day and then you were like saying it like
So you know what the degenerate
Come stick it think it really carefully how you talk to me. You're saying you're calling me. I'm not talking about you
Okay, okay. Oh, he said that you live a degenerate life. So I still understand the generous. No when you live
When you do
Generate I have aphasia. Okay. I got you. I got you. I'm sorry. I'm not trying to rush you
So I go but why did you bring him up the other day?
Well, um, I was going through some shit and maybe I
I think people sometimes fucking try to manipulate shit to, uh...
to make people on on you know, oh
That's disgusting that you know, that's really sad
Well, so here's the thing the only people that should do that is
the
Adobe Acrobat file man. Yeah, well, okay, so but who but why'd you bring it up and who's like what?
What is it? What's the relevancy?
Am I in my chair? I don't know. I don't know dude. You were playing games when I was talking to you
I don't know what the fuck. I don't know who was that I
Calling me brother like I know him and I assume it was
It said t y
But why why are you fishing more mint more I just know because I know some so I'm not fishing for information my friend
I forgot about it, but then I'm somebody in the chat was
Asking me to ask you and so I asked you and now it's those Johnny boss or Johnny Boston
supposedly
Over it was a king cobra. I don't know if he died
No, no, this is separate incidents and Johnny Boston died and back in
love I don't know 17 18 2018 maybe so he's been dead for like five or six years
well then how yeah dude you know that people so the generate lifestyle people
Broadcast in themselves have been going on for a long time, right?
And these people know about like years and years and years, not just low cows, but not
just cows, but like people, like people that aren't, uh, like journalists, uh, journal.
Live journal people people that uploaded to their channel not knowing anyone was watching them
You know kind of shit
And it, it's grown into a culture and it started, I'm going to say back in the 2008 is, I mean even before that, if you want to go socially, there were people in chat rooms trolling way before that.
Well, yeah, I mean, it's been, I mean, the trolling's been around for hundreds of years, probably in certain contexts, but I'm talking about like.
Are you talking about Chris Chan, or like that person?
You're talking about this degenerate shit
where people put people in little classes, like lockouts.
That shit has been going around on the internet,
at least my eyes since 2003, 2004.
He was 32.
And that's neat.
So when I used to do it, that was then.
I
Talk about trolling is like an ancient is a kind of like gangstalking it's been around since Jesus, right?
It's a gangstalking if you're doing it by yourself
Uh-huh. Well, no you need a gang technically to be a gang stalker
Yeah, or if you're if you if the person is putting it out there live for
Everyone to see and it doesn't say private when they have that question
Unlisted private or public? What do you want this thing to be?
You know where they do it like I mean if you pray if you private a stream then nobody can go to it, right?
Well, you put right and you put Chad on you have that choice to turn Chad on too
But I just don't know. I don't know how that would
How that people would be able to see the live if it's on private, but
The guy JT is a friend of psyche. He keeps pushing a key cobra drink
Okay, so JT. Okay
So we hold on guys
What are you saying the guy Jaycee were you bothering King Cobra? What's going on?
You're pushing your ring
Jaycee my chat
Really, because King Cobra's death is really irresponsible if he was drinking.
But I don't believe any chatters bullshit, and you believing I sodomized myself was really
weird.
Hold on.
No.
I was told that you put a brush in your butthole on the camera.
But someone said that, I didn't say I believe it.
I just said, oh my God, that's crazy.
I know, okay, so cool.
So cool, I believe that you said that, but.
I didn't say you did.
I had no idea.
I didn't see anything.
I just talked to you on chat and you put me backstage.
I came up, I wanted to talk to you about it
and you threw me backstage or I forget what it was.
And I wanted to talk to you about,
what Christians think of sodomy in Catholics, obviously.
And how people would react if they were accused of sodomy
in a public forum and how they would react if...
I'm sorry, so isn't sodomy just like anal sex,
it's like male or female, it's like, you know,
or you know, sodomy or something like that?
Yeah, it would be me sodomizing myself.
or somebody sodomizing me for pleasure or pain,
you know, whatever it is.
It's illegal in some states.
And if you own that material in those states,
I hope you're not in the south.
And there is no material, there is no video.
There's the video as my naked ass
and sitting on the camera.
So that's what I did.
Okay, so you just said make you were just naked you weren't there was no hairbrush. I
The hairbrush thing because I brush my hair and I sing into hair brushes and shit. I
Guess maybe you got the idea. I know some youtubers
Had stuck one in her pussy, and maybe he just messed up the stories because he's unoriginal and
I think a lot of these people are unoriginal. I'm an original
I got influences in my life that teach me how to do what I do
You know for art whatever art. You're doing art. You're doing
Livestream and this is our art. I believe you're doing art. I'm doing art
Doing DJ work. I guess I'm playing music and talking my commentary and and honestly, I wanted to
touch base with you because
The other night that was bad form dude. I felt like I was bad form
I felt disrespected by you.
I don't feel anything about any of the guests
because I'm talking to you, you know?
Yeah.
Well, just, it was confusing.
I'll say my point of view of it.
It was like, just confusing.
Cause you came up with this weird look in your eye
and you were like, Johnny boss.
And I was like, yes, what about Johnny boss?
And I was like, who's that?
And you were like, Johnny boss.
And it's like, I don't know.
You were just like not responding.
Like.
So people remember, I'm not expecting you to remember Johnny Boston, I'm expecting other people to, well that's what I'm saying, I'm expecting other people to remember him and maybe they don't, but it's an example of what can happen when you are
Pushing the limit for the content, right? You're not doing you're getting out of your comfort space
What you admit to you doing all the time, right? Oh, so you're talking about me. So what would I do?
specific what I do specifically that made you think about the home and bring God up a second hold on what God
God are you gonna hold on I want I want this stage
Can I see this stage backstage real quick and just or just promise you're not gonna
Because I have fake visages, I have fake odds, I'm not sure, I'm like, fuck, it's like, I can't figure out what to hold on.
No, no, it's me, it's me, it's me.
Okay, good.
Is the sage person okay? Guys, what do you think in the chat?
I don't know about it, I don't know anything about the sage, I just wanted to tell you something.
Okay.
Yes.
You got me blocked in the chat, by the way.
You're blocked? I thought I'd go through the block.
You had one of your fits, you had one of your fits last night, you fucking blocked me.
But I am block you. Did you try to talk? No, you know, you never gonna block me. Yeah. Yeah, you fucking block me
That's I'm just telling you now. I tried. Yeah, of course. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You know what?
It's like I admit like I I
Get I get into my no, no, no, no, it's okay. It's okay. You don't have to apologize. I expect it from you now
It's just fine. I do I do I do but no, no, that's okay
That's okay. I'm not gonna accept the apology. You got this fucking retard up here talking about sodomy this whole fucking time
What's going on with the show? What's going on? Is this the new topic now? Oh?
Well, I want to get to the bottom of things. No, no, no, no pun intended, okay?
What's your retard in your mind?
This is fucked up, dude. I can't contribute to this. I'm gonna leave.
Okay, bye.
Why don't you? Why don't you?
Sike, I just wanted to give you a heads up on what J-Dog's trying to do. He's trying
to divide you and Vita. This is what he does in communities.
I see that.
He wants to cause drama between you two, and he tries to say the grease is against everything.
We never were friends with Tony. We terrorized Tony. We got him kicked out of his fucking house
J-Dog picked up Tony because it's like the island of lost freaks. They just collect each other
This is what J-Dog does. He went to Tony had Tony do all that bullshit to y'all now
He's trying to say it's the grease
He docks his people, he has facial scanning recognition.
This is servers now property of the allied master computer.
Can you like Tony Bologna doesn't look like it?
Yeah, that's their homey. They put him up to do their dirty work.
That's what they do, psyche.
Steve, this is what J-Bolt does.
That's exactly what they do.
Divide no, I'm not dividing up to you. Who brought up beat up. I'm not being beat up
I have to say yesterday I have to give you a warning jade up because yesterday not only did you call
Stargazer bitch, and she's like a nice nice lady, and she didn't yeah, I apologize
I'm spawning
Psyche bro this fits a
Who's been saying to the character you want that tow truck gone again watch you do it bitch do it bitch do it
Careful wish I dare you I dare you do it bitch do it because I got you
The problem is that like not like a lot of people keep
Trying to like like bring her up and like and then I can it's just a dart and it's like no
I'm not bringing her up. You know what beta just doesn't like me wants me eliminated from your sector psych
And a lot of people that do not like me are just ganging up
That's what they're doing I love and I love I love beta and it's like and it's like I do
If she gets called names like on panel and stuff like that. I'll defend her and stuff like that
But yeah, I apologize. I shouldn't get that. I shouldn't get that. I apologize
There's also several of her mods in her chat that hate me and it's like and I I got yelled out for like just deleting comments and stuff
Exactly you know exactly bro. It's not fair. It's not fair like I shouldn't I
But it's like and I don't so I I don't want to be responsible for it
But I should you know, I guess I am responsible for what people say on my show, but I mean it's like
It's like
I want her to have her mods and who's in her chat and just run her show like she wants to
I want to run my show like I want to if that entails me not going over to her show or maybe she's not
I hope I can make up with her and stuff, but it's like I I wish people wouldn't keep trying to like
Yeah
I want you guys to be best friends with me when he's talking to you big shut up sage
You're the one causing the debauch. I'm causing nothing
They've been fighting before I before I even came into this fucking thing. They're fighting for reason be before even me
No, it's just recently. That's what they're fighting about right now
Like he and Vita have always been friends until you came along your foolish shit psyche was the last fight you and Vita had
besides besides this one
About other bullshit, right?
constantly but he's like on the on the air and then we like but it's like we're
really cool one-on-one and then it's like other people get involved and it's
just like everything goes to hell you guys are cool one-on-one because she
could try to get me like she's trying to manipulate you that's what he says look
I mean, I don't want to be
So essentially scum what happened was J-Dog dox betas number
Your boy your boy RG dox beta your boy RG dox beta
No, you're lying lying lying
None of that sure I know the dox beta you're fucking full shit chips age
Shit you doxed all of them. You had Tony do it
There you go. I don't even know Tony you just okay. Okay. I don't
Messages were me and him talk show me him
No, I know who he is but I don't know him personally they're saying I contact him. I'm cool with him. No, I'm not
He was using Tony as a cat's paw to Doc's people
They're just making shit
It kind of makes me like it as a cast pop being like a tool or something. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes party a scapegoat third party
Lies lie and that's what j-dog. I don't know
Lies lies lies. Do I have that kind of power? Do I look like I have that kind of power to get that sight to me?
I just I don't
This guy this all goes kind of way over my head like because I don't understand like why how I'm
Involved any of it like because I never did anything anybody cuz you're a nice guy and J. Dogg tries to take advantage of that
No, I'm not taking advantage of nobody. That's your boy RG your boy RG your boy your leader RG
You should be ashamed of the black man
But you're getting more white you are half white so like there
Are you guys in the scene that fucking followed RG like a bitch?
Yeah, they are
He's telling me you're not part of the grease
You 100 part of them
No, j dog, where did you get my incident report from because that was a diffused issue
Where did you get that from your buddies?
What buddies
A police buddies
Exactly scum. Okay. There you go. I want to talk about my police buddies. Okay. I have police buddies by the way
I don't have I don't have your internet report on a background check
Is that I don't have I don't have it pay the 20 I have to check my studio. We're back
Yeah, you can get information I didn't I don't have your stuff. I don't even know your name scum
I don't even have your legal name.
I don't know anything about you.
I see your face scanning technology scum.
Don't believe it.
It doesn't matter.
Bro, now I'm saying I have facial recognition technology
now.
I talk face all the time.
I grow beards.
But I used to have a clean cut face.
I know.
And my ID has a clean cut face.
No, scum.
I don't have your information.
I don't have anybody let me show you this little cute boy see that guy
That guy is much
Not much different than the guy you see here, right? Yeah, I'm gonna say that
You see my face all the time
all I see is about
35 years of aging on that little boy
Right
In a hell of a lot of chemicals and fat, but I I I want to say this dude
You looking up that little boy or this 38 year old man shit
Hadn't if you did it or somebody else did it
No, no volition. It didn't matter
You came up with what?
You want to press me on anything else?
Or is that the only thing you want to press me? That wasn't it's coming. That wasn't scum on the no issue with you
Scummy is the name. I do use all every once in a while
But um if you mean it in another way, um, that's disrespectful
But what they're talking about is having a single woman get scared for a life
And I know how that can scare somebody
um
And, uh, maybe I've said some things that are shitty to even that person you're talking about, but never had that intention.
Um, I think if those are true, then it's true. That's between God and them.
150 fucking times and digging your hole more
There's nobody digging a hole, but
Yeah, well they're just gonna try to tell you all kinds of bad things about me that's all they're gonna do and they're gonna
Weird thing psyche have I ever get anything back to you in all honesty? Have I ever
Yeah, so so why do they these people they're trying so hard to get rid of me?
Why is beta why's all these people so against me to get rid of me from from from here? I don't understand it
But they're treating me like if I get something like the worst worst thing ever, but again, it's like crazy wonder that shit too. It's uh, yeah
Jealousy sometimes
They're mad because I'm on you know what it is
They're mad because I come and I I'm not a troll like the rest of them
I honestly try to get along with people and be cool with people and I get try to get along with everybody who has a channel
I do hang out with trolls. I don't hang out with trolls what trolls
Well, yeah, well, I'm gonna say this if you use trolls if anyways
Anyways, never use the troll. Never. Um, I'm gonna say I've trolled
I've always trolled, but that's something natural. That's the way I show
Love to people. I'm it's not like evil evil trolling
But the way I show affection is joking at you or, you know, right playing with you clowning, you know
You can have the gesture go up to the king and the king says off with its head
Right
That's all the times now. We are civilized. I'm gonna bring this up again
It's not
Go ahead have a look at your chat and go everyone look at your chat right now. There's something on this cat
I want you to have a look at but you don't have to
The rest of the rest of the chat that's been there. Okay there. Okay. We got our first pull up guys
It is Jod lying go ahead and vote yes or no, and that but you know
Maybe I can do that. I have to leave though
Okay, once yeah, it's a no regular. Okay, that's right. Yeah, I mean, it's like, you know, it's just for just for
purposes of you just to see but the
idea of the chat. I do have a computer now, guys, and so I am able to run polls and things.
If you have a suggestion for a poll, let me know, and I'll try to start one up. Okay,
so JDoggLeft, okay. Okay, well, anyway, you put no. Okay, yeah, there you go, guys. Yeah,
I do have some cool stuff going on now, so I can't make a poll. Let me see if I can.
I'll Jay dog. I can close it eventually. Let me see. So
Yeah, I got a lot of cool stuff. I like cool stuff going on here
So guys, let me know how the polls go in. I can't do this. They're like I'm on stream yard
So I it's a little bit of a different
Amanda any I need to redo Amanda. Hold on. Sorry. Sorry because I have I figured I come in here today psyche and
use my magnetism.
I mean, I'm just doing everyone's standard mods
just to keep it even Steven's only night mod
is the managing mod.
So guys, the most powerful mod here
is actually a robot, okay?
In case we are, okay, so I think everybody
that's modded should be modded so far.
You're back. Okay. Well, I hope oh, yeah, I hope you're feeling good spunky. Let me see what's happening. Let's see
Good to see you guys you're feeling sick. I'm sorry
Hey, I hope you're doing okay. You know, I was you know, I've been going through different
thoughts and stuff about the show and you know, of course, I really do want to
Keep it a friendlier vibe. Like I want to keep it a friendlier vibe
I want to stop like you know encouraging Kate and stuff like that. No, I'm gonna like you know
Put stuff in the more positive direction like you know
Monetizing it in the sense of I guess you can
Take over the you can actually put one person now backstage just me you put me back stage
And then you can run the panel basically like you want to for an hour
I'll be backstage running it you want to rent the panel for like 25 bucks
You want to just rent the banner space for an hour 10 bucks and that's
Nice trade-off for either like the clapping system or the sponsoring system. I think it's like more positive direction, but
We can try it. How can a nightbot be a managing bot? It's a robot? Yeah. No, I don't know. He is
I think yeah
I think it's
I think it's I think it's pretty fair, but
um, because
Uh, I don't know. It's just like
I've had some issues. I had some issues with people hiding people
Like as managing bots, I'm not saying you or anybody, but
um, I just think it's better
I'm not a bunch of people that keep everybody at the at the standard
You know and I also want you guys if you are able to join the mods especially to join the discord because
I mean, even though apparently this guy owns my Discord,
now I'll show you the picture again.
Yeah, apparently he says he owns the Discord, okay?
He posted this photo this morning,
and he thinks, he's like, oh, he's like,
oh, I'm so funny, I see things he's so cute and funny, right?
Okay, so anyway, I'm gonna keep that photo there,
but here's my Discord.
link, invite link, because I can't just have one.
I have to keep updating it constantly.
So here it is in the chat.
Go ahead and join the Discord guys and mods especially,
because I want to have a chat in private
with the moddy mods, okay?
So...
we can get on the same pagey page, okay?
Mod meeting, mod meeting.
Yeah, we need to have a little pow-wow.
And also members, I'll do the members only things too.
I did not, I should, I'll do that next, I'll do that next.
But yeah, he, and I'll get, I'll see everything.
Yeah, he's, I mean, God, and he has a...
Well, he does have a nice smile. Hey, Chris. How are you? Yeah?
Here yeah top messages again. Why is it doing that? I don't know
Oh
I have it, but it's too, it looks too complicated for me.
I'm considering going to stream elements,
or stream, like, if I might have to do that,
because, you know, it's like, I can't,
I really want to maybe cut down on the panel
self a little bit sometime, but I guess panels are fun,
but sometimes it gets a little overwhelming for me.
Better user friendly, but you'll still,
you'll have all this monetization you'll have to encounter.
LBS, that's the standard software
without monetization features.
Okay.
Yeah, I mean, I, yeah, cause it looked like
I opened it up and it did that infinity thing,
like where it's like all the mirrors facing a mirror
where it's like, it felt like I was,
hey, money for 20.
Guys, I think I,
I say, Jamie, we'll have to brief Amanda on the meeting.
Yeah, I'm waiting for 20, okay, so,
I don't know, people were hidden last night.
I just, 10 dollars also through a glass of menudo.
Oh my gosh, well, I don't know about that.
Okay, so.
Tripe?
Yeah, Crystal, by the way,
if you guys go to my community wall,
I put, I found this video,
it was probably from six months ago,
where it was like Crystal versus Christine,
and they had this Golden Girls thing,
and they had Sandman as like a still getty.
It was kind of funny.
I don't know, you can go check it.
It's kind of classic of my show.
I don't know, I think it was,
I hope my show is still good,
but it was pretty good back then,
Vibe that was that it was just like hilarious like and but we'll see you know, it's like I really
I'm trying to like pick the pick the wheel of my own show
You know because a lot of people are trying to say I own the show I own the panel like you know, Tony Baloney
For instance other people and other gangs and affiliate. It's like guys
It's really my show. I don't have a gang war on YouTube. Okay. It's like
That what I say goes basically it can like pretend like you know how God he has the name God pretend like I'm God of the show
And here's the thing you are Lucifer of your show
Yeah, but yeah, but Lucifer is like the God of the earth, right?
So I don't know. I don't know. I'm just saying I'm saying go with the small
Show me a god, and whatever your god is, fuck him, dude.
God is, God is, I'm a pantheist, I would say.
Okay, sorry.
Yeah, excuse me.
See, do you know what that means?
I thought you were a satanist.
No, you've been blamed it once though. Yeah. Yeah, you were
So there's different kinds of I would say Satanism, you know, I would say you're more
Luciferian vibe. Okay. Yeah, but it's like that's different than like the Edge Lord, you know
No, yeah, the high school guys. Yeah, I know. Yeah, it's more like the
Kind of like a, like a, it's like basically a little bit about, um,
You know trying to rule yourself and like you know, like I'm not trying to like say
No, I wouldn't say I believe in the high the most high and I would work worse
Of course at the most high but I think that Lucifer came as from the most high and Ezekielus as he was God's covering cherub
The most beautiful angel the leader of the heavenly choir and he but then he had a pride
They wanted to be God and so God gave him the meaning of the earth
and it's kind of
It's to show them how difficult it was to even be an imitation of him.
And so, you know, there's a ways of thinking.
It's philosophy, basically, but I have a spiritual side is the, is like the creator, like the, the, the...
That's everything. Pantheism. So, pan means all, right?
Yeah.
Okay. Well, that's...
But you're very fluid.
So, you know...
Right, because I figured after this year of knowing you, it's been a year now, Psyche.
I met you during beta, I met you right out of the hospital, maybe.
I was talking funny, right?
I still talk funny.
I think, yeah.
Well, you can talk funny, I mean, you're fine, but I think you're the same scum I've
Yeah, you know I'm not different than I ever been and that's what's crazy is when people
bring up these I'm surprised in all this shit and it's like you've known me for seven years.
Me you've known me for five years. No, these people. Oh, yeah
They've known me for five years. They've known me for three years. You know, it's like stupid
It's kind of rich. You know, I went through a brain injury
A year and a half ago. That's it
Other than that, I am going into us
I feel like Christian and he is bringing me towards it
believe in evil and there is you know somebody has to control that evil and
you can manifest that evil and control it yourself because I believe whatever
big G gave us he gave us free will
Right, but I would say there's so but I'd say good and evil are
dualities and and we all contain the possibility of both and we can choose which direction we go in as
beings right and so
But it's also like a process. We're constantly evolving and it's like even
We do the best we can in life. We certainly like gonna be 100% perfect, right? We still have never to improve. Yeah
You don't like the free will lookie or plucky what the fuck free will you know what I like free will it is because
Well, it's gonna kind of free will versus determinism, right?
Is it's like every is everything like just already determined and there's no choices or do we have a choice to?
Improve or to change for the better. So I thank God made us the way he won't made us be too
and that is planned for whatever, you know?
And Satan can do whatever he can do,
but ultimately you and God,
if you work with God, you can defeat Satan
if that's what you want to do,
or if you will something else, you will something else.
If you wanna will, that person did,
Get sober. You'll do anything to get that person sober in
Including telling he should be fucking tossed off a pier
Well, that's right. It's awesome up here. That's not actually tossed off a beer, but I'm gonna toss you off a pier
Unless you get some shit done in your life
Kind of say some crazy shit, right?
Are you talking to me?
No, nobody in person.
Nobody.
But say you have some will to do that, right?
You want us to do that.
And it's a good thing like to help somebody
get their life together or maybe help them get healthy.
Like fat guy, right?
Big fat guy that has potential.
Right. Yeah, what about it? What about a big thing like the new background? I
Kind of disappeared into it. So I'm testing some other ones. Yeah, you need lighting. Can I tell you that?
Okay, I need some light. I need to get I did. Oh, yeah
I need to order a light. Let me just order
Or I would say you can get one of those photo lights, but um depending on
Well, see the ring lights can do certain things, and you might not like it, but certain ring
lights have different colors, you can be cheap with it, you can be expensive with it.
You know, I don't know what you set up is like. I'm I want to be I'm relatively I'm relatively cheap
But I'm just kidding. I'm not really cool. You picked up looking at some little
LED of my little kitty and alien
He got a little kitty LED somebody sent you an LED
Neon. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah, that's what I said. That's me. That's the neon. Yeah, this my kitty over here
Yeah, I have that same one. I got it from Christmas last year. Yeah, you have this one too. Yeah, I got it from Christmas
Did someone send it to you or did you yeah, it's funky spunky spunky
Yeah, my girl bought me that for last
Christmas and it's a little bright because of my vision problems
It burns into my eyes or I guess my retinas maybe
So the shit will like I can still see it from last night for example
I had it on a little bit last night
So I have this little
alien on my retinas or on my vision.
Does that make sense?
Yeah, they kind of burn into your eyes.
You know I'm not blind, right?
I'm not totally blind.
I thought you said like legally blind maybe
where it's like you have that little bit of like a.
Yeah, I have vision, right?
It's just fucked.
And then sometimes when my medicine isn't working,
It can get worse and then, um, especially if I don't take the convulsion medicine, I
can't even get out of bed.
So it's not just being blind is my ailment, right?
It's being able to do anything.
So, it's real shit, so if you hear things about, I don't know.
I'm faking my shit, it's not fake.
I never thought that, you'd always said that you could see it, but it takes you a little
bit longer to sometimes look at it.
I appreciate you for acknowledging that because I've had a lot of people think that I'm totally
blind, but it might be a communication breakdown led to that point, you know?
Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, it's just like they hear the word and they think that you're saying, you know,
Well, everyone thinks that you're a cane. Yes, Steve, you wonder. Left on stage.
The Braemings. Yeah. I understand that, you know, you might have had like a, you know, a traumatic,
traumatic brain injury that affected you. No, no, it wasn't a TBI. It's an anoxic.
Okay.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It's weird. It's uh, it's lack of oxygen
What is chat saying because uh
Something about they haven't mentioned they really didn't mention like psych. No, I like
you
I like opening and seeing psych
Yeah, it says say can we have a moment of silent wait? We did at the beginning of the show for
Kinkobra, we'll take a malt shake hamburger and fries. Jamie said okay. Well, this is a this was a
vanilla affogato, which is like a vanilla
Basically vanilla milkshake with like a shot of coffee in it pretty good, and I have a pumpkin something or other too
So I'm getting my caffeine in
Yeah, rest in peace. Can't go by, you know, the world will never be the same, blah, blah, blah.
Okay, so...
Was he a Saintess or was he an Agilord Saintess?
Well, I mean...
I think he might be.
I think I saw clips of him and I really...
and I was told that he could come on the show.
Why am I... these are my Diffie Dahmer glasses, okay?
I'm wearing them inside so I look cool, okay?
but uh wait he's got he's got sunglasses on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on hold on
Why haven't I kicked you out Tony the conductor you're Tony Bologna now, okay?
That's what you look like
Put on a hat look at that hairline Tony
Are you what are you Eddie Munster or something with the hair white of widows? I mean, it's a widow's peak
But it's like it's like half bald. I mean, it's yeah
I like my I like my widows peak. It's a little I have like yours. I come and I have a similar widows peak
We have like we have like this like
See like kind of like a more wider one
Is it it's too soon about Jeffrey Dahmer? I don't know. I've been joking about it for too soon
I had this whole thing, I read a letter and I don't know if it was real, if it wasn't,
but it was a letter from his neighbor about a potluck, it might have been fake, a potluck
dinner they were.
Cookout where he brought a plate of food would you and that here her husband ate so much of the food
he was like a
Like he was gonna pass out because of the food was so rich
You know, it's it's not good to like certain information
You shouldn't know I I think well me at me or or anybody
Well, I read the whole book.
But yeah, in Ali Messer Computer,
after relying on other people's good will to get by,
it's called having the good will of people
by being a decent human being, by not being an asshole
and doing horrible things to people.
That's why I have good will from people, okay?
You can maybe learn something from me
about how to treat human beings
and not treat them like fucking garbage, okay?
Like you have, and so Tony, Tony Bologna,
you're gonna get it back today, okay?
Okay, Tony, I'm not scared of you.
Okay, anyway, it's called scamming people, you dummy.
Oh, look at your dumb face.
I'll have to get this off the whole screen.
Look at the dumb face.
Hold on.
This is what he looks like guys.
See that?
Actually, it's more of a,
look at it.
He looks exactly like that emoji right there.
Doesn't he look like that?
See that little green emoji?
He looks like-
I like the green emoji.
That's my emoji.
Well, you kind of look like that too, Scum.
Not gonna lie.
I know.
I'm gonna say that.
Looks like Scum shaved his head.
That's him.
You know what?
Look at him.
Look at the teeth, look at that.
I was shaved it.
Is that a fake smile telling you that?
Tony are you are that a real smile? That's your real smile. Why are you doing a peace sign?
Is it oh, it's adhesive is that oh is that it? Oh, yeah, that's ally
That you Tony. I thought it was him
But it's a piece of his representative because he says this server is property of ally master computer
That's what he says either that or it's been doctored because from what I don't think it was dog
Who would someone a doctor to look like that? I mean that one's in a doctor photo. It's like that
This is a natural photo. I've seen him on somebody's
Tony is that your grinder photo is that your photo that you put on grinder? I want to find out
And they were on screen for a couple of minutes,
and they didn't look like that.
And the size of the face isn't as...
Well, I think it might be him.
Is that him?
That's Tony right there, that Tony?
That's him, right?
I'm not trying to disinformation.
I just feel like he had a bigger...
more college and you know bigger trip on trip and beep let me see I don't know
maybe I think they were like I don't know I think they're mouthing off of me
or something
Yeah, just remember guys like if like if like I get pissed off. I don't I don't care about kicking people out
Even though it's like you might like them and stuff. I'll give them another chance. Well, the trippie can be okay
I love everyone
You love everyone that's well
I don't like some of these like a lot of these names are docs or docs. Did you hear me say no?
Oh, no. I'm sorry. I
You said I said I love everyone equally and then you said you love everyone and I go no
So, you know, that's what it is. I mean far. Okay. What else is yeah, you can't by the way, Crack-a-duh
Crack-a-dawner came in here yesterday trying to hit Docs. And so Crack-a-dawn is really you think Crack-a-dawner would do that
Well, the name is Kraken Donah, so it became
And he went to the channel and has
Beep Beep and Trick Kick or Unmage
And all that as a member
The guy is a partnered person
He's got a monetized channel
He went to the channel and he's got all these
memberships and how like
subscribers and shit
Yeah, you know you're really you're so stupid. You're so stupid Tony because oh thank you. Thank you. Thank you, Kate
Hold on. Oh, thank you. Thank you, Kate. I appreciate that. Okay. Yeah, I have I have a little I have a litter pan
But all my cats are outside right except Louis right next to me. I'll bring her for a second
So allied guys if you see um, and you kind of oh, yeah, I think we got we got it already
Okay, thank you so much. Is that all let me see all messages start asking them question
Um, is out the does that allied got hit? Thank you so much Nancy. Thank you so much
But is allied hidden? Yeah, she should be hidden now
Okay, thank you guys. I've got my mods are on it. My mods are on it already
Thank you so much on the way or but they better be paid for they if they're not paid for it
You'll be reported to the police by the way. Oh terrorist rayers here. Nice to see if you're a destroyer
You're sweeping the chat
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you will be reported to the police and
Dominos will be suing you for
Mexican pizza lady will not be happy. Okay, Mexican pizza Loka will not be happy
Hey, this is Kate. Thank you for the thank you for the donation Kate. This is Lola and Lola your
Lola, do you poopoo on the floor?
Do you poopoo ever on the floor?
No. Oh, she's like, no, I'm not a dog.
I'm not a dog.
Only dogs poop on the floor.
Cats are smart.
I go outside and do it.
And that wasn't poop.
That was tobacco on his table.
You, not Kate, but whoever said that is a dumb fuck.
I mean, the person that was saying it was a dumb
I threw my boots on my Jordans just to prove a point.
Okay. Well, why would you do that?
That ruins your shoes, though.
Not when he's nudes. Oh my god, please don't guys. I don't want to ever see Tony's news
I'm gonna refer to that. I'll be pleased. Are you sure? I don't I'm gonna turn straight
Rather see
He turned you out that much. What did he do to you? He struck my channel 11 times and then
Then and I don't get into it anymore. You know, yeah, you're fine. I might maybe I'll pretend I know
Okay, pretend you know I don't but I assume it's horrible. I
Didn't fix it. I was I was not saying that Kate
I was saying that whoever said that the other night like I think her name was kiss my cheeks and
Eldo, oh who actually were on the server on discord or somebody the night before I the night before yeah
The night before on the on that same server. I
I got a little notification that there was somebody posting something on that server. It was called
Clip and sip or something and it said
H-O-L-O-C-A-U-S-T
Dot G-A-Y and so I sent that to beta. I was like beta look at this website in the next day
Eldo and that kiss my cheeks
We're in there in that server doc like you know posting the pictures of my table or whatever saying it was my floor because I guess they're retarded
They think I have a wood floor and there's a carpet obviously, but it's okay. I'm not gonna. Oh
Come on. Okay. Come on
Beta's cats are different kind of breed where they're kind of like, you know, these little fat cats these cats are
you're lanky and so the cat's fine the cat's not hungry i have i'll show you the box of cat food
i have hold on one second if you're gonna like you know put me on the spot i'll just show you what
i've got for cat food
guys are wondering like what i feed my cat and it's like no i've uh here's what i got this is what
Yeah, I got this box, okay, I bought it, okay
Okay
Okay, I get that and I did this one too
So, I mean it's like a thermal nurse this
They might just sit on their own diet.
They're just like, I get these big,
they taste like a 40 pound thing, I don't know what to say.
Anyway, cats look well fed.
Thank you very much.
You're a clean cat owner, dude.
Yeah, I appreciate if you don't believe you.
I appreciate you to spread the rumors about my cats
because I don't say things about your animals
except your animals are beautiful.
And so don't, yeah, my cat's the healthy guy.
You think you can be a Trixie?
No, no, you've been good.
Did I ever do that?
Okay.
I just don't, I don't know if you should be.
Yeah, I know it's very happy healthy. I wasn't and Sam and said I wasn't throwing tricks in that picture
It was just I was picking him up and that he was making a joke about it. I don't
He made me look like I was starting to play football. Would I ever do that? I would never do that. I would never do that
You're calling me mini man some really
Are you going like
They don't like to shred it. I don't know that this one is not shredded. I think it's yeah
No, there's a norm. Oh, is it shreds? No
It's the solid one
But then I guess our mean oh come on
Vicky come on. You don't like you don't like cats cats are the best
They're not mean but they're they're they're good judges of character. So they're maybe mean to the people that
There's some dogs can be mean, though. Think about pit bulls and chihuahuas.
Don't give them problems. They're just chihuahuas are aggressive and pit bulls are fine.
They just bite hard.
Tigers bite hard. They just don't mean to paw at you.
I don't know. I've never met one.
What happened to Siegfried and Roy, or one of those two?
Oh, yeah, Roy, Roy, Roy.
He had a stroke.
We got attacked.
No, he had a stroke, and the tiger sensed it and tried to grab him.
Well, I don't know. I think it was waiting for his opportunity where the guy fucking finally had you know, it was not like
You think those boys with those tigers tiger. They did of course. They're tiger trainers
I mean, that's how they train tigers of whips. I mean, like, you know, the tigers aren't just like, oh
Let's play with these like, you know, game. I thought they raise them from like, you know, baby
Well, you know, there's a story of this guy. I'm not it's not about tigers, but this guy raised this little chimpanzee
Hey, what's up, Alex?
Yeah, I'm Mo.
You're having a great day too.
Okay, yeah.
The guys, they went, the chimpanzee got too big.
Malifornia, right?
And so they put it in like,
they put it in like kind of like a behind bars
and then they went to go visit it one day and like.
We're bringing a sandwich and an attack them and bit off his nose and stuff. It was terrible, right?
Can I tell you that I know it's weird that you bring that up? That was in California, right? In Covina?
So that guy he got he got mauled by a chimp. That wasn't his chimp.
That was another chimp.
No, it was another chimp, and he had gotten jealous
because he brought Mo a cake or some shit,
and the chimp got jealous.
Yeah, oh yeah.
And Maldon, I mean, he used to sit out in front of his house.
And he used to, so his house, he had a monk,
he had the chimp and it was a big deal in the neighborhood.
I grew up kind of, you know, in the neighborhood
and they had the chimp out front, sorry, the chimp
and people would go see the chimp
and the city told him he had to get rid of it
because it's LA County, right?
Was Moe the humanity though? Oh Moe, the humanity? Remember they said it, he looked like maybe part human, the outline?
Was he? No, no.
No, okay. No, that's a that's one of the
Yeah, I know what you're talking about. No, I did a DNA test in LA County guy
This is a Mali County guy with that and he was protesting the county and we would hunt when we go by and
Kind of shit, you know, but we found out he got mauled and you're talking about it and that shit happened
You know those
Those people were doing wonders for those animals,
but the problem is those animals,
they got addicted to cigarettes.
And I think the whole place shut down.
I know that recently the whole place burned down.
So who knows?
Like that whole area was covered in fire.
So less, two years ago.
Well, you know, California has these notorious winds that, you know, and rush that and so fires kind of spread pretty fast
Malibu and
You know what?
Oh, yeah, you surprise
People aren't well. Yeah, but you know what but it's usually because of like
The fires are started, maybe accidentally or maybe not, but then they're spread by these
winds and in the dry brush.
But then they have these women's prisoners that are trained in firefighting and, you
know, it's like the circle of life.
They put out the brush fires and then, you know.
Idiots are flying drones for YouTube clicks is when it gets too far.
I used to watch those fires when I was a child on the hill and I watch them burn and not
thinking it caused me lung problems now but I'd watch them drop that red shit on the side
To keep it from burning. Did you grow up in any foothills or anywhere?
I grew up on a peninsula, so next to the ocean, you know, oh, yeah, well, you know what it's like, right?
Well, I never we never had a we never had a fire there, but I know that Malibu
notorious for having fires
You know, we had I mean I grew up in to I was in thousand oaks Malibu is right over there a
Gora Hills
Scott fire so much
Yeah, well, unfortunately there were fires like last year. I actually didn't know this year earlier this year
And I got a message on my phone saying oh, you might have to evacuate. I was all freaked out like oh my god
They didn't get anywhere near here fortunately, but
Yeah, it was kind of scary
If I start fires you finish them. Oh, that's good. Good. Good big your sisters friend
Put her arm in a chimp cage at the zoo and a chimp bit a chunk out of her arm. Yeah. Oh my gosh
She jumped over the barrier. I mean that is yeah, it's kind of
Yeah, it's asking for it
Well, yeah, you don't jump into like an animal cage at the zoo the tarpon would jump in the tarpon
Well, no because it's tar defense now, but oh, yeah
But you know what happened to the dinosaurs. They thought it was swimming pool
I saw an Arnold Schwarzenegger in a movie
Falling them, but I don't think it was real
Because I think probably down right you drown in them
They told or else you look like the tar baby. Have you ever seen the tar baby or that?
Don't say don't say it's
Remus, it's not race. It's not race. It's actually
There's a no no it's not racist there's actually a story called the tar baby uncle remiss and they make a baby out of tar
And then the very rabbit is all tangled up in it because he starts fighting it
I'm very well of uncle remiss. I'm very well where I'm uncle
Uncle remiss. I love uncle remiss because these are these are folktales most of them are African based folktales
Adapted yeah
Song of the south
What happens is Bill Cosby, the gatekeeper of Disney, doesn't want those stories to come out because they've been, yeah, that's who bought the rights originally.
Yeah, I don't know that one. We're gonna look that up on Bill Cosby on Song of the South and that was a rumor
It was an urban legend. So remember that I'm coming from urban legend
Crypto mythology
Look at it says
Snopes will might help you. Oh, yeah. No, it says it right here. It says is
Sigma Bill Cosby, let's see
Does Bill Cosby own the rights to song the South?
It says, no, that's just an urban legend.
Bill Cosby did not buy the rights
so that it would not be shown again.
If anything, he has allegedly expressed concern
over the amount of African-American history
that has been lost, stolen, or strayed.
So-
Well, I'm concerned with what he did to those women.
Well, yeah, but I mean, I guess-
I mean, that's kind of a dark topic.
Let's not bring that up, okay?
I think he did already spend, you know,
it's time for that.
It is a dark topic, but there was one that got away
that I can say that somebody I hold true to my heart
would never lie to me about.
But go ahead, next topic.
I mean, I think it might be a Psyop too, because it's like he did spend very little time in person for that, like, you know, it was also like a very luxurious person, like, more like a work program, kind of.
He was in his 80s, though, right?
at a Department of Defense, you know, I don't know.
It's interesting how it goes.
I don't know, maybe it was the insurance company.
It could have been anything.
By the way, doxing is illegal. Let me just tell you California's rule about doxing, doxing, law, and so it says California's law defines doxing, making it a misdemeanor to distribute personal identifying information to incite third party harassment, unwanted physical contact or injury.
was passed to create a private right of action allowing victims to sue for damages and seek
equitable relief even proceeding under a pseudonym. The law criminalizes electronic
cyber harassment. This is Penal Code 653.2, criminal liability. Please don't dox because I don't want
to have to pull the police on you. Psyche, I don't even know your first name. My name is Bob.
My name is yeah, I know you as my name is Bob Smith. Thank you so much. My name is Bob Smith and
Yeah, yeah, what and I look at one two three Apple Apple Apple to drive
Yeah, like I I don't I honestly don't care
I call you by your suit in them because that's the respectful thing to do
I'm going to yeah, I mean guys even big big
Guys Vicky, Vicky knows doxing is wrong. It's like you must be me
Come on guys. We all know well nice. It's not nice. We don't know what somebody
What if somebody was to go to that person's house and hurt them, right?
You would definitely be charged for the criminal things because they trace it right back to you doxing the chat, right?
So you don't want to put the you don't want to do that. Is that what's happening?
Yeah, they're doxing people somebody in the chat some poor dude. Yeah, I don't know who it is, but
Name
The initials it's that there's no one there's no name. It's just the address and so no idea what the first numbers
It's I think it was like three. Oh, I remember it was kind of like something it was it was deleted immediately. Yeah
Okay. Interesting. The mods are on, right? Okay, we have King Cobra.
Yeah, I'm just curious. That's not the real King Cobra, because King
Cobra passes away, so Empress Chinchilla.
Good try, but you know because I can't see I want to make sure it's not me
Right. It was Empress Chinchilla. No, it's not you. Empress Chinchilla was just trying to go under King Cobra
Not only are you using someone that's passed away like yesterday, which is like really bad taste, but to call yourself Empress
Is bad taste and then to call yourself Chinchilla is bad taste. So you're just like a disgusting
Human being, okay, whoever you are, Empress Tumela.
You know, King Cobra, you can say his name.
He went by his name on Facebook.
I mean, yeah, well, he's passed away now, so.
And if they have a memorial, I'm sure people will fly out.
Well, I mean they can probably televise it and then we can people can just watch it on
I don't think I should just go care his father
His father doesn't know how many people not just like so some of the so-called trolls
Actually care about that man, right?
He might be frustrated over the years, but I'm sure some of them care about him
I know that I've seen people go to bat form
Yes, can we do a Ouija board I don't have a Ouija board handy, but I can like pull cards or oh, yeah
By the way guys, I will do I'll do some
If you would like me to pull a card, I'll pull a card,
but I'll do a 15 minute reading,
and I'll try to get the camera set up above it.
I can add another camera,
and then I'll do like a 15 minute reading for $10.
Super chat or cash up, if you're interested.
You can have a longer reading.
You did a reading.
Who did?
You did a reading for me.
When?
The other day.
Did you taro or or Persian hafiz?
She hasn't done one for me for a long time, you know, I think I used to when I met her
She wanted to she didn't ask me for permission, but or she did maybe I was open to it anyways, you know
I'm always open sometimes
You're good.
I just, I did my like, I'll stop again,
the lecture, so no, and everybody's,
what, Psyche and, no, I'm not Princess Chinchilla,
Chinchilla's a porn bomber of my show.
That's all I, I just know that Chinchilla just tried
a porn bomber under the King Cobra name, okay?
So, not very nice.
We know that King Cobra is, you know,
passed away, rest in peace, okay?
Just someone called you a hard R. Okay. Not good. I've been called a hard R and F.
I've been called every word you've looked, you know. I learned that the little palm sticks
in the stones can break my bones, but words will just annoy me. So.
What's great is I use a...
different app to stream on and I you can just flip over to video only mode I
know it's rude to the chatters that support but I have such low viewer
count it doesn't matter well I'm thinking about like maybe like it's like you
know if people don't start
You know asking for readings and stuff like that because because of panels who are distracting and then they're not
You know buying the advertising space or anything
I'll probably just stop doing the panels and switch over to stream labs and yeah
Get it up right there, and I'll do like the TCS because it's just like I can't just like
stream every day without any support like I need like you guys to like maybe
like somebody to participate right my YouTube memberships to gift I did tell
yesterday well no they don't give me they don't like they don't give me ten
like they don't I never saw them give me any memberships to give me see if it's
on my computer though I'll see I'll try it out
because I paid for the 10 I gifted yesterday,
but I don't see it.
I don't think I get three ones.
See it right here.
Oh, I do have it.
Oh my gosh.
Hold on.
I can send, hold on.
I can do it on my computer.
Okay guys, but you know what?
These ones are not,
I don't get a benefit from them,
but you know, you get some free memberships.
Okay, I can do it.
Yeah, when you get to a certain level.
Yeah, here we go guys.
I'll do 10.
So we can get some more green in here, but yeah, there you go
Congratulations
There you go guys
Okay
Cool, it's pretty cool. You know, I've never been a I never was able to do that
There you go. Thank you for letting me know because I can do all of a sudden do kind of cool things through the
Through using the computer. So I was never able to do that before it never gets people in here. Yeah, I like that. So
Pretty cool
Berry with like, okay, got you Berry
Berry, but why don't I see you in chat? Is it sit? It says all mess it up. Does anyone see Berry? Oh, there he is
Berry
You got a very
My sugar bear
And yeah, my sugar berry psyche has to buy
Yeah, I was able to I just gave 10, but I also gave I paid for 10 last night
No, no, no, I I've wrenched Barry, but I'm saying I pay I
Got 10 gifted memberships yet last night, and then I got 10 to give away today. So that's pretty cool. I'd like any more
Pretty damn cool
Yeah, cuz it's kind of shitty that you don't get to pick the people
Right. Cloud trolls do get membership services. Yeah
And it's like well this dude contributes more like what the fuck I
like
So if you had YouTube premium like Twitch when you have Amazon Prime you get a free
subscription every month for example
And you could support a Twitch streamer
Yeah, oh, yeah, I would have mentioned that guys. I am I'm streaming on Twitch right now. This is my name on Twitch
I'll put it in and you go if you have a yeah
If you if you have a an Amazon Prime account
Then you get a free membership to give away to the streamer of your choice on Twitch. I would like ask you to consider
You know, it's you know put a couple bucks close to my pocket
And it's you know free to do if you would like to do that
I'll mod you on on kick or twitch if you do that
if you do that, okay?
So that's on Twitch.
Hey, there you go.
So their content policy allows all the panels and everything.
Well, yeah, because, I mean, sometimes they get porn bombed
and I don't even, I forget to leave it over there,
but it's like, they don't even check really.
I think they're just trying to still build up
their membership base.
Got an affiliate?
I'm talking about the cake.
No, no, um, Twitch, Twitch is more the video gaming one, but I am on kick too.
I'm on kick, but I tried to stream to kick today, but it wouldn't let me for some reason.
I couldn't put a category for the show, so I just did kick on Twitch instead.
You can see my, this is my Twitch base right here.
Interesting, they must have changed their content policy
because they used to be super strict on anything.
Oh, well I think it probably has to be reported
or something, I'm not 100% sure, but.
No, their mods were literally in the,
Chats and shit like you couldn't you couldn't like you couldn't get away with somebody in
Indeed, you know DBR off kind of content, you know on um, on a on tiktok
They have this AI
That um, it's like if you say like another if you say YouTube on tiktok
They'll restrict you if you light a cigarette to blow smoke if you do anything on tiktok, they'll just
age-restricted. Okay. Put your hand to your mouth. Are you? Yeah, but people do. Who comes out? It
knows you're smoking. Hey, Ivana, how are you? Okay. Yeah, they know you're smoking because
then they just age-restricted it and they don't, which means it doesn't come up in the in the feed,
like the scrolling, so nobody will find it pretty much. But
That's the way I would say it.
TikTok is trash.
I like, you know, TikTok is so, they're like a lot, it's friendly.
I like how friendly it is, and I also am able to do my quick, you know what, the quick
readings aren't really good for YouTube, because people are like, oh, they're so short.
Like on TikTok, I just like to do the quick readings.
Here I want to do the longer readings, so I'm going to probably make it, like, I'm just
going to do.
or the paid readings on this channel.
And if you want a free reading,
go to askthequestion.tiktok.
I'll do free readings over there.
And then if you like a longer reading,
you can either book a private reading
or just a short reading over here
which will be discounted because it's on the air.
So if you're interested,
I know it seems like a lot of people
are not really into,
hey,
Kate, Kate, you wanna do that, Kate?
Kate, are you sure?
Kate, I really don't wanna have smoke with you, Kate,
but if you're gonna say that,
and that's a very ignorant thing to say,
and that's, Kate, are you gonna go there with me?
Let me see, I'm gonna get your reaction if you say yes,
I will be taking care of you immediately.
Kate, you wanna go there with me?
You wanna go there with me, Kate?
You wanna say that to me in my chat?
Do you know what?
I never disrespected you in your chat, Kate, okay?
You know, I never went over to your chat
and disrespected you or your chat, okay?
You're gonna say that to me on my chat, Kate.
Kate, content creator, colleague.
Kate.
Tell me.
And guys, by the way, it's a fake Kate, okay.
Yeah, by the way, by the way, that was,
like I know some people in here.
Um participated in the like the little like the little lynching. Okay. Is that the real cake? I don't know if it's a real cake
Yeah, there was a little there's a little I did I did
Thanks to I don't know and I
Would call it that I would I would call well no drug would mean like there was something like drag
Like drag drag but drag but drag is usually but if you're if you got dragged, it's usually
Because it's true, so it wasn't true. So it was like a oh, okay. I get it. Yeah, that's what I mean
Okay, is that a real Barry? I thank you for the donation by the way, Barry. I appreciate that
214 subscribers to videos. Okay. Yes, big Kate. Okay. That's not the real Kate
That's that can't be she doesn't have
214 subscribers Kate has like thousands
Yes, she
So if it's a fake cave, I can just be happy to be happy to hide her.
She's got to have more than me.
Um, you know.
Yeah. Well, that's the way, I don't, I'm, we'll buy, if you're going to,
I don't care if you're real or fake, you're not going to say, I'm a,
I'm a cat abuser gay man, that's not, you're not going to call me an abuser.
That's, that's slanderous, okay?
Yeah.
I never abuse an, I never abuse an animal, okay?
That's that's me. I would never I think that's I think it's it's sick
You know and it's like and to accuse me of that group you don't deserve to you know be in the chat
So you're sure also well
Guys just be like if you just like if she's gonna say shit like that
And she's not gonna apologize or take it back. I did give her the opportunity
Then you go ahead and yeah
She had no reason to comment
And she had no reason to say that and I and also Kate. I never I would never like
Get to you, but now I'll talk to the other Kate that cut the real kid comes in right I
Just don't know and Barry said it's her
It is her it's her it's her. Yeah, no, she can join she can join but I will read her
I'll read her right on the air. I'll read her okay
for saying that, because I have something to say about that.
If anyone has something to say about me, go ahead and say it.
Go ahead and say it.
You muted me quick when I, honestly, I came here, if I'm coming back, I'm coming back
because I'm coming back, dude, I'm saying sorry.
And I I that's why I said within this time
I'm gonna say sorry or you know next time whenever I feel the need to bring it up because I lost my shit and
but if you're gonna say some shit and
Not be about I say something bad you did I say something to you though? What did I say to you?
You've always been apologetic for other people's shit and it's the elbow fucking more shit up between you and Kate
Remember that one
Yeah
That's a real Ivana by the way, but I'm subscribed she now you can go ahead and subscribe to get a bunch of you if you want to
Hey, Kate, bye. These are your cats
Scum take meds. Well, thank you for the
Like I said, like the cats are fed like I showed you all like the you know 40 cans of food in the 50 pound bag
So the cats are fine sleeping. They're not like, you know, but
Thank you for the super chat and if you guys if you want to say something
If you want to say something rude like that, I do appreciate if you put it in a super chat, you know
Or else you'll probably be hit timed out. We're gonna put the panel in so we can get content
Oh, you want a positive today? Sorry. Yeah, but you're yeah, but that's okay. No quantum gaden
You're about to be hidden, but yeah, I don't even know if you're just reporting that. It's like that is disgusting and
Okay, bye Kate Kate bye
Bye bye bye bye Kate
You look like a ogre. Okay, let's see. Oh, yeah
Well Kate, you know Kate just said you're casting to see a bet they look sickly and so that is a bitch thing to say
And you know shit
Sometimes
Who's that?
That's a I didn't order pizza. That was a prank or something
It's all right, can you put my name on all this?
I asked for paid for you can take it
Okay, was it paid and this is paid for you can leave it outside. Thank you
Yeah, but if it's paid for you can leave it out there, but it's just otherwise. It was just some some
Neanderthal that I did not order
It was somebody on the internet. I'm a celebrity. I'm sorry my forehead
My forehead
Look at this
Neanderthalic
Oh, I mean I have what I have one too. I have one too, but it's like see you can think of my words
It's okay, it's okay
Got a bunch of fucking lump scars and shit. Yeah. Yeah, go Barry go live and expose Kate please and like yeah
Let's go, you know, I can talk shit to Kate. Okay, you want me to talk shit because you know, I was always
Okay, yeah, Kate, you know, you know, you don't want you don't want to smoke for me Kate
You don't want to smoke for me. Okay. Hey
Yo, how are you doing, Scum-A?
Hey, it's better, better than last week.
Doing better is good.
That's good to do better.
I say doing better because we all go through ups and downs,
you know, roller coaster of life.
Yeah.
Well, I'm enjoying the panel.
Can you chat now?
300 glow is hotter than K.
Cold chills.
Yeah
Yeah, okay. Oh, Hannah, you know Hannah
Are they saying something because I saw them be quite rude to me in
Be this chat, and I don't know if and they were laughing about me having HIV or something like that
Which I don't think is a very funny thing to be laughing about
Yeah, well, so Hannah like what was that about? I didn't know I was watching that
Yeah, I was I saw you like laugh
But I don't have
Okay, it's Hannah gonna have sex with you. Oh, thank you so much. Hmm. Thank you so much
Okay, thank you so much. Uh, thank you, Alan. Hey scum. Would you like a short short reading?
You've been you've been gifted a short reading. Would you like a short reading? No
No, okay. You would not like one. Okay. Well, do you like a short reading?
I am passing a few cards for you.
I looked in about an hour ago, you were up here, Scott,
there was a couple of other people up here too,
and you all seemed to be fighting and bickering about something,
so I left.
I don't know what is going on, but yeah, it's it's been a little bit of you know, a little bit of drama lately, Doug, and yeah, someone's been way, way inappropriate.
And people, you know, I just got a pizza sent to my house, not paid for, of course.
So, you know, I don't think the pizza place here will deliver pizza if it's not paid for.
Yeah, they won't come up to your house and collect cash from you. You got to pay when you order it like you know
No, doesn't do that anymore either do they I don't know
Domino's
Okay, I'm sorry. I
Don't think that anymore restaurants don't deliver shit unless you've already paid for it pretty much
Yeah, I mean actually I had a door-dash that was unpaid for I was like I don't even know you can get
Unpaid for door-dashes. I thought the COD. It's kind of ridiculous
So
A code or you have a number you have a thing for door-dash right that you have to have on your phone
Yeah
kitchen obscure accounts like the guy that cooks in his he cooks Indian food
but he cooks it out of the ghost kitchen in this house right then Dory's back
to eat the pizza
Right well, I went to I went to an Indian food place and thank you
Hello, and I had Indian food and they offered us the Giorno pizza
only
The Giorno pizza not the worst, but not the best. Oh
It's pissed
Psyche I'm sorry you're getting your ass. He's having a bad time
But something about
J-Dog coming on here and fighting with somebody else and I said well, it's you know
It's not fair that you talk about personal incidents in my house and and you've got that information
somehow so
Yeah, what's up? Yeah
mm-hmm was it a nice thing you you muted psyche doesn't think you know maybe talking
I'm still not hearing you you hear me now. Yes. Yes. Okay
Doug my friend Alex has sponsored a a reading and
Scum's not interested. So would you like a wait? Is that Alex Myers? Yes. Yes
Oh, if it's Alex Myers, I'd love. Yeah, I'll do that for Alex Myers. I thought it was somebody else.
Thank you, Hannah.
Doug, are you also going to read my tarot cards? Is that what it is?
I will. Yeah, if you're interested, I'll read up your scum.
If you're offering, I'll say yes. Absolutely.
Okay.
Thank you for doing that two for one because, yeah, Alex Myers, she can do.
Polk art. Yeah, that's fine
Okay, I'm just and I will pull them up once at one at a time. Okay. Wow. Okay. Let's see those the balance of the world
Okay
Okay, wow, okay, so this is the H-O-R-R-O-R Horde Tarot deck, so this one's for Scum
and then I'll get you next, Doug.
Okay, so first we have the three of swords, so what this would indicate to me, Scum, is
that there was some kind of major heartbreak, I'm sorry, there we go, three of swords in
it felt like you got stabbed in the heart, maybe a betrayal, but just basically it's a heartbreak
card I would say. And then we have the Six of Pentacles. So this Six of Pentacles is a card of
By being generous this is for you this first come I'll do I'll do you right after I'm done
This is the first first scum
So the so six of pentacles a spirit of charity. I think you know, that's the way out of this heartbreak is
to be just to be giving and to be generous I think that
If there's some kind of karma or anything or also this is also some kind of success that you've had
that will lead to you being able to
to give more and support who you want to.
Next we have the queen of swords coming up with a tower.
Okay, the queen of swords is usually a woman
a woman that has maybe been through a lot
and is now had enough of it and.
You know, she has that sword and ready to cut something, you know, cut off if need be and the tower is a sudden upheaval
And it's like these coming up together. I mean, it's like it says I'll read the card to you
It says they were young healthy wealthy beautiful free and in love and it said until tonight and so
Could have been some kind of crazy shake-up, and then this Queen of Swords says an unbiased take of tale of independence
And so this is a very independent woman
basically
Standing up for herself. Okay. Yep
And then
We also have another Queen. This is the Queen of Pentacles. Okay, so this
It looks like this woman has a couple queenly energies associated with her and
The pentacles is material abundance, and I would say having this woman by your side is
Basically a good luck charm. There's abundance will follow her or success will follow her everywhere
But then we have the six of wands six of wands is a victory card. And so I say
victory in
In attracting or you're keeping this woman
It says a victory at what cost and then it's like it says obey. Okay. It's just a obey on it
This looks like that. What was that movie with the
Yeah, and
and Elsa says
You know rowdy rowdy Piper there's a movie where you put on glasses and he was able to see behind the veil and all of a sudden
the advertisements have these subliminal messages in them and so
That might be that's this queen might have some kind of subliminal
Power or something on the subconscious, but I think it's been some kind of positive way
Oh, I think it was a rowdy rowdy Piper, right? What was that movie? No, I was just kidding
I don't remember the movie
But I know Vinnie Raffer sick is often say obey on them. I think it's referring to the same movie. I believe yeah
You might not know who Vinnie Raffer is, but he's a local
Self-promoter who has stickers all over the place here. Yeah, Vinnie stickers
I love some Vinnie stickers somewhere
We also have this I pulled like a card of advice, and you know what we got another
I think this would indicate to me scum is like this whatever woman this is is like
She is probably an Empress because she's got all the I pulled three Queens
I three out of the four Queens the deck three Queens and yeah, and this one is like a movie is that three Kings?
No, you're thinking
That's my it's like it's like Norman Bates's mother, but it says courage
Yeah, I think this might be from the show you saying I have three queens in my life
I'm sit. Well, it could be three different women, but it could be a
qualities of one woman, right?
And so I think it, you know, you're,
we should be an Empress.
The Empress is all the Queens in the deck, right?
And so you got three out of four, right?
So I would say, if you have a good woman,
I would say hold on to that woman
because she seems like a good woman, right?
And maybe if there's a lesson, yeah, you know.
I do it daily.
Okay.
It sounds, you know, so far pretty good.
Everything you said seems to fit.
Um. Uh huh. It does. I think it's probably fit well for a lot of people too, but yeah.
Yeah. But I think the car, the right cards will come up at the right time with the right
message. Right. And sometimes things will stick out to me. Um, specific things with
a specific person, right? But let's go to Doug, okay? I hope you like that reading
Oh, you mean Scamay's first, okay. Yeah, I just got this. Yeah, I mean you're you're you're next. I'm next
Okay
Thank you so much for for Alex for purchasing that reading. Thank you so much. Okay
so
Let me pull six. Okay. Okay. Okay
That's not gonna be okay
Okay, well what's coming up first Doug is this is this the seven of swords and the seven of swords is traditionally known as the thief card, okay?
And so there was there some kind of like large that larceny
Done to you in the past or the recent past or something stolen or something like that. I mean, this is an interesting card
You know, it's like
In this card, it's a woman, but in traditional cards, kind of like this guy escaping the circus with everybody's cards.
The Seven of Swords, huh?
Yeah.
Seven of Swords.
I'm sure we've been robbed, but not lately.
Okay.
Marceny, right?
Oh, yeah.
They took something that was mine.
Absolutely, that's happening.
Who is it?
Okay.
Yup.
The word's Marceny.
Is there a question?
Is it A4 or something?
Is it Larsonous?
Is it A4?
Okay, that was some kind of prank or something.
I have a crazy
mentally ill stalker, I'm sorry.
Hopefully you get to keep the pizza yourself.
But I did not order it.
I'm a local celebrity
so I
am being harassed lately.
I'm sorry about that.
Yes, sir. I didn't order the pizza. It was a mentally ill
stalker of mine, so
I have some mentally ill stalker, like they're just a prank.
I'm sorry. I hope you get to keep the pizza though yourself. Okay. Have a nice day.
I apologize for that, you know, it's a, you know, it's an interesting day, right?
It happens.
I'm having audio issues, I'm just going to-
I mean, if they paid for the pizza, I would be happy to eat the pizza.
Okay, also, so Doug, also, we have this Eight of Wands.
Eight of Wands is this card about a very rapid communication, something, maybe about
Stolen or something like that because it's coming up next to the seven of swords
Yeah, it says change it's coming something is in the air action it the time is now
Where will you be when the big event happens?
And so something coming very quickly whatever it is. It's usually some kind of communication that you will
Know about very quickly. Okay. It's usually kind of represented by like these
Right but here's the here's the good news, okay
So we have this this ace of pentacles ace of pentacles is like a seed of prosperity
It has the ability to grow into something
Big even up to the tenant pentacles
And so this is something's gonna be handed to you that you will be able to maybe invest or
grow from a C form into, and this is right, I would say right around right now, this is happening.
And maybe it's in this palm, I would say maybe you have this already in your hand. It's like,
maybe it's already something. Okay. Yeah, just just from this particular card, it says,
manifesting your material goals, that's what it says. And so, whatever it is, it's like, you
Something that you have a goal for right and let me see if I can find out what that is about. Okay. Well, this is a page of source
Okay, so page of sorts. I would call the spy card. So somebody is maybe looking or
Watching and seeing oh is they're looking to see how your investment is
Someone's watching your investment, right? And maybe I would say not necessarily in a bad way, but they are paying attention to
Maybe what's in your hand right now also?
A page also, it's usually, you know, a younger person or the beginning stage of something,
right, that can grow into something, something bigger, but this was an interesting one.
It says, it says, new ideas, positive, change, and curiosity, okay?
And so these might be some of these qualities that you're dealing with right now.
I would say looking at these two things at these two cars together. Well, this is interesting. Is this person looks like this guy is like in a
Kind of litter box or something or a trait. It's like I'm sitting down
And she's over there. She's over it with like almost like a voodoo doll or something like that
Hmm. I see the guy it looks like a secretion doesn't it? Mm-hmm or something like that
Yeah, and so these these are interesting because they have a lot of symbolism
That is not maybe the traditional but there might be something that stands out to you about this because it looks also looks like some kind of
Educational setting maybe okay. We also have this high priestess the high priestess card is this intuition
You have a strong intuition about something you already have the answer you might find the answer in a dream high priestess
It's also finding the answer in silence like
an inner knowing and
Being receptive to the to the message coming through so there will be this message
You already maybe already have a feeling about this or will very soon, but you know something about that
Okay, and this is about the king of swords
We got another king of swords the king of swords says in absorbing a tail of intellectual authority in
in this tradition, okay, and
King of swords is a great communicator often an air sign. It doesn't have to be
and
A sharp mind also
Goes along with the the manifesting
The currency the money. It's like being able to to
Manifest out of thin air and also I would say very high intelligence. I mean this I think see the big brain right there
There's a big brain. Yes
And I think you're from the black lagoon
Yeah, and these together. It seems like you've got the correct balance of the
the instinctual and intuition and the brain power, okay, and so I'm gonna pull a cart of advice
because
That mean that's very I don't are you you have a partner or not?
I live with my wife
Okay, because so that your wife could very well, I mean women often exemplify this high priestess energy and this
Since it came out with the king and it's like it seems like it's a great balance with you
Listen, I've always done better with someone than without than on my own. Yeah. Yeah, I always have
because it's
Motivational it's you know what I mean
Mm-hmm. Yeah
Keeps me doing doing things that you know that it's left on my own. I wouldn't do
Yes, and I think that like I think that is a
Very powerful role with you know heterosexual couples. They can often
They work great because often because they have that perfect balance of the masculine feminine and also the
Just like you said it's like you know having a partner will motivate you inspire you and you know
You're able to manifest because these two energies coming together like alchemy, okay, okay
So the advice is it says the advice is the hangman
And so this one says we dare you to look at the world from his point of view the hangman is basically saying to you to
not take an action at this time but to
keep an eye out and to look at something from a different point of view before you proceed and
After you look at something from the different point of view the hangman is always able to get you know to get free usually
It's not literally hanging
But so I would say they take a pause before
Taking a big action about something and look at something in a different way and so I would say maybe
You know ask your way ask your partner your wife ask your wife about it
Because I think she she has this intuition about something that
And it looks like it's something that will change into like large prosperity. Okay, like grow into something
Something big. Okay, so I hope you enjoyed that reading. That was great. Thank you
I see the people in the chat. There's people in the chat enjoyed it too
Great, thank you. Uh, yeah, they got lots of comments
Well, yeah, and uh, I really thank you for your kind. Yeah, it's all good. Yeah, it's all good
And I always say with my readings, I don't say,
well, this will happen in the future, blah, blah, blah.
I say, these are the current energies
and your future's up to you,
but this should give you an idea of what is possible
and maybe what is happening right now.
And so, and I hope the right met.
And also, if something didn't make sense today.
If watch watch to see if
It pops up in your mind again in the near future because it might something might be relevant there like a little hint
I always would like just just keep it keep things in mind. You know and
You watch this one. So yeah, thank you, Doug and thank you for the reading. It's like yeah, I gotta go because okay, dude
I feel me home shortly and I just thought I came by earlier. Like I said, there was a couple of guys
And I'm not sure who, but they were pretty yelling and cursing and shitting and I was like, yeah, I'll look in later.
Well, Doug, it's been a nightmare a little bit lately, but with some of the stuff that's been said, it feels like a mob mentality a little bit.
Brilliant, you know going way overboard with the slander of me, but you know, okay?
I'd expect it me answer more. Thank you for being here though. I always appreciate you
Great guy, I'll come up again soon sounds good
Always a pleasure
Okay, guys. Yeah. Yeah
God yeah, I would not say
You know, I would not necessarily do that interpretation of the hangman
because the hanging man traditionally is just hanging by his foot and he's
going to meditate a posture and he looks pretty relaxed. Also reminds me of Odin
who was hanging and he discovered the runes because he was able to actually
like meditate, see things from different perspective and figure something
important out, okay? So...
So what's up? Not my son. Okay, so insane people cannot help being insane. Well, okay. Well, maybe that's true, right?
So what's
What are people talking about are they because if but this person has the different names of the same avatar and they're being very rude
And so I'm going to be
See
I'm gonna be hiding that person. I don't need Elvis made you do it. Well
You know go talk to Elvis Empress Chinchilla is live on kick sending more pizza. Well
Empress Chinchilla can go put the pizza up his butt, okay?
Because
What someone knocks on the door does that? Oh?
You're okay. Okay. Okay. I mean I understand something sometimes, okay?
Yeah
Well, Jim John I
Actually am but you know what it's very very hot right now first of all and so I'm like sweating
Also, I've been wearing t-shirts instead of like my planals and so you actually get to see how skinny I really am
But you know I've always been a skinny
Cocka loco
Yeah guys get rid of this
Cocka head
Okay, but Jim you didn't say in such a rude way, so I don't really I'm not gonna ban you or anything so
But you know what yeah, and well that's saying something so what are you guys celebrating that?
You know these some of these communities are so toxic that they might have a physics like physical effect on people guys
You know that there's people that are actually
You know, and I really I feel really bad
But um, like I feel terrible actually there's people being harassed that are actually have a
you know terminal disease, okay, and they're they're being
harassed and
Right, and it's like what kind of sickos are fucking with with like sick people
It's like it's just it seems like cruel
Definitely mentally ill, okay?
Yeah, God, you're really not a person like this other thing and the effing FATG OTS. Oh my gosh
You don't celebrate it most you're just mentally morbidly curious. So you watch
Okay, well, but I'm not talking about me because I don't have a terminal disease. I'm perfectly healthy
I'm talking people with somebody with an actual terminal illness is
being harassed attacked and
You know, I think that's fucking wrong
And it's like, if you're involved in that, shame on you.
I'm not talking just you, anybody that's involved in that.
Or celebrating anybody that is sick or anything.
And may that negative energy go back on anybody
that's projecting that on somebody else, okay?
Okay, I am perfectly healthy.
I mean, I'm alive, aren't I?
Wouldn't I have like, you know, died a long time ago
if I wasn't, let's see what we got here.
But yes, some of these comments are ridiculous. And you know what?
Mods, mods, can you get on top of these people?
Empress is not getting it. Empress is not getting a reading. Empress Chinchilla can go
Jump off a pier like a scum would say, okay?
Sometimes you get involved in harassing the person. I know it's sick harass guys you're gonna harass somebody terminally ill
Do it who agrees with that or celebrates it because it's like
pretty sick and so and I
You're talking about scum a who's scared. Okay. No, let's not spread better. Okay
It just seems sick. It seems sick. Okay. It's just the same thing as like some of the low cows are actually mentally ill people
Yeah, you have to put on you have to put on all chat Jamie
Look at the little wheel and go all messages so you can see the whole chat because sometimes they are filtered out
I need mods to especially have that setting turn on all because I see every comment. I want to stream your
Thank you. So thank you, Ilya. Hold on. You see
You can't time you can't time out Ivana because you're not a mod Ilya and see there. She is I
Don't really want oh, it's Christine here. Hi Christine
So what's going on? Yeah, some of the stuff. I've been you know, I've been also talking to some people
I won't go too much into detail, but I've been hearing some really really disturbing
Stuff some people are involved in and it is sickening and it is wrong and
I
Can't have any of these people in my chat and so I you know if I have to hide these people and
Protect my channel. It's like obviously
You know these people think that they have some kind of power. They don't of this channel
I will they'll be sorely mistaken if they're gonna fuck with my channel. Okay, they'll be sorely mistaken
my channel is
Quite quite protected. Okay, they'll be sorely mistaken not only by you know the
Material forces but by the spiritual forces, okay? I
Wouldn't play okay
Thank you. I'm not timing out
You know, you know or about another finder fine. You didn't Jamie. He's not a mod. He's not even a mod
So you can't do that. He just he just hides them for herself
Yeah, you see they're just they're just there's just
Joking around you don't worry about it
Like let's see that it's kind of hard to tell sometimes that just I know them. They're playing. Yeah
But you know, I don't think it was funny
I'm on I like personally
was pretty hurtful like
You know all the people harping on the stuff the other night that was not I didn't even get a chance to defend myself really
but it was really untrue and
Really sad cystic so many people that I knew saying you know
And I thought we're like friends of mine like you know saying horrible things about me
That's what really hurts, like when your enemies say stuff about you, of course your enemies are gonna say shit
When people that you consider friends or on good terms with are like agreeing with them that is
But it's okay. It's okay. I don't even probably don't care whatever I know
But you know, I'll have your back if you ever, you know, we're attacked unfairly. I still will okay
I don't I don't have anything against you. It's just like I wish people would sometimes have my back, right?
Okay, that makes more sense.
I'm just kidding.
I don't think so.
Yeah.
I mean, it's like really, but I'm saying, you know,
doing that stuff to me, yeah, that's kind of like,
I don't like it, of course, it's hurtful,
but there's people that really don't deserve it.
I should have left your wrench psyche.
We would have gotten rid of everyone.
Okay, oh Riz. Oh, yeah, I didn't like just unmodge and modded everybody because I was just
Yeah, I'll be much. Well, I don't know
You ever everyone
I've not everyone just like the the bad people right, you know
Well, we'll give you a chance because I know you from another chance, so
Okay, but
Otherwise, I think I have enough mods and I really prefer female like female mods because I think women have
some better judgment about things but
Okay, yeah, well if you he does
Probably is a reason for it, right?
Okay, everyone good. I want to make sure everybody is having a nice
nice day and
Yeah, does anybody have let's do a Q&A. Let's do a little Q&A. Look, I can put up something too
I can put up something that says Q&A and
Then you can ask me
What are you like?
I might be probably, do you see it?
I don't see it, I think it's still in there.
Okay, yeah, I look like some kind of weird library
or something.
Well everything's frozen, shit.
Can't do anything right now, shit.
There you go, there you go
You should mod the man at CFF if you prefer mods that were fully for the undies
Hold on is Riz already is behaving hold on Riz
Is he misbehaving?
I thought Riz was the, okay.
Yeah, Riz, never mind, never mind Riz.
Thank you though.
I need somebody with really good discernment about it.
And not that you're a little bit too strict.
But.
Okay, well you didn't know but you can block it for 10 seconds. You don't have to do it for whole day
Riz, okay? I think they were just thank you. Oh, thank you Christine
Riz just just be in the chat because it's like you know, you can't let the chat antagonize. It's agonize you, right?
But I get I get like that too. That's why I'm trying to like let mods take care of it and you know
but
Yeah, he didn't say anything to be blocked
And so, you know, I don't want to be too strict, but, but, like,
Christine knows exactly what I, what shouldn't be said and stuff like that, right?
Airbnb, but, uh, let me go look at the down and something, hold on a second.
Guys, you know how hot it is here today?
I'm sorry.
It is 83 degrees.
Wow, it is a hot one.
Okay, it's the garbage day, it's garbage day.
You know what's good about not having a wrench sometimes
is that if you have a wrench,
Especially people people that are my mods and people that are mods in general. I would I prefer people that are my mods to
Be unified with me and so sometimes if a person is like not unified with me they should not be a mod because
then they
Can just be themselves because it's like if a mod is out there saying shit about me like I kept seeing this before
I can't have them as a mod. You know, I need the mods
Not talking shit about me. I don't know if that makes sense, right?
Like I would never talk shit about the somebody I was a mod for I wouldn't like publicly on another channel and make fun of them
And stuff like that. I would not think I'd be remaining a mod for very long
You didn't have your wrench for a few hours. I take it back. Um, I I'm sorry money for 20
You know, you're not you didn't do anything wrong. It's just like I had too many mods. I need to have like kind of like a
The Mods they have are all good, right? I don't have any problems with these people the whole show
So
Yeah, so if you're not a mod if you're not a mod then
You know, I don't I don't really care if you say stuff, but it's having mods
Making fun of me like the other night and beat his chat like I would I went back and just watch the chat and some people were saying
Oh, psyche is hung himself psyche's hanging from the Raptors
Psychi has cancer like he has AIDS and then some of you were laughing like Ilya. I saw you laughing the other night
It wasn't funny
That was hurtful. Okay. Yeah, don't worry about the rents are like, you know just for
people that are you know
Really solid really solid
Wanting to support me not for people that are gonna be laughing and teasing
Me stuff like that, right? So I love I love you guys, but it's like a little hurtful some people like
participating in some of that stuff
It's really negative, okay
and
I'm human and so it might be like got hurt a little bit, but you know, I know
It's a trollish personality.
What can you do?
You can't do much about it.
Trolls gonna be trolls, right?
But, okay, so I will show you,
which one should I show you?
I'll play my, should I play my new intro again?
And how many people are here?
42.
I already played it.
Oh, come on, Ivana.
Yeah, I know.
It was terrible.
Ivana, I was so disappointed.
I was so disappointed seeing it.
Ivana punched you.
I know you're not weak, but you were quite mean to me, but it's okay. I know you're just
Troll gonna troll. Okay, so I'll play this video I made yesterday
Golden wings glowed in the candlelight
Crowds came running just to see the flame
But envy was the price of fame
And now he stands where the echoes fall
With tarot in hand hearing every call
From praise to venom in the same breath said
But the fire in his eyes burns gold
to see Rudy. Rudy, you want to come over and say hi? It's so hot right now. See, it tricks
the city behind me. You can see it.
When you're Q&A, there's a Q&A.
So go ahead and ask me whatever question you want to ask me.
If you want to ask a rude question though,
send it with a $5 super chat or you will be timed out.
That's going to be the rule.
Or cash out, by the way.
I'm not kidding.
I don't answer anything.
But if it's going to be rude, it's
going to be a troll question.
You're gonna be in trouble unless you send it in a super chat or up. Whoa. Thank you, Dougie. Thank you so much, Dougie
Thank you so much. Appreciate that so much
Wow, let's see you
It's gifted a membership. We got rabbit. We got Berlinetta
Pinkiebrain calm our friend. Oh, and it's always sunny in Tulsa
Congratulations. You've just received a
a gifted membership to the show.
You have now have access to our special archives
with material too hot for YouTube.
You'll also get a longer reading
at whenever you ask, or basically so.
And also cool emojis too. I don't know if you guys have seen the emojis I have
But I think I designed some pretty cool emojis for the chat and here's the member emojis
And there's what there's a troll emoji guys. I like I thought about the trolls too
so and
So here's the emojis
Yeah, look at these cool. It's like how cool those are though. Yeah, I admit I did a pretty good job
We have the troll, the goddess, the evil eye, smile, we have the chaos, the funny face,
the BKG, we have the ghosts, we have the grandma, we have the gong, we have the reading, we
have help me, we have the goat, and we have the eye, and so those are the emojis, okay?
Thank you.
I do have beautiful kitties, and thank you so much Doug, that's awesome, and I really
at the bottom of my heart, it's very, very nice of you and I appreciate you.
Yeah, so you guys can see, you guys can see these cats, these cats are happy cats, they're
loved, they are my babies and so imagine, you know, I'm not gonna ever have kids, right?
So I have cats.
You know, I know they're not the same as having, you know, of course, human beings are a lot,
Very different to raise but for me
This is gonna be this is my family. Okay. Can you be a mod?
No, well, Riz. I did I just made you a mod and you started timing out people that were joking around and stuff for a whole day
I mean
But I do like you Riz Riz, you know, you can if you want attention though you can
You bought yourself a membership up your name would be in green and I would notice you more
You don't need a
I really have the best mods, I think, as it is right now.
I think everything is perfect right now.
And I just want to say thank you, mods,
for keeping the chat safe.
It's been a little bit crazy.
But I appreciate you being helping me out.
Can do very much without you.
Guys, I go into stages where it's like,
I feel like, oh my gosh, like,
like, yeah.
What's gonna happen like like is the show gonna be like if I get that like
My having as much fun and stuff like that
like
sometimes it's like
Little bit gets a little bit too crazy, but there's the people that are like
you know, even it's in the chat and
At least nice nice to me like
Just I have a I have a great circle of protection around me as well as maybe an outer circle of trolls trying to penetrate into it
But I have either I have a I have such great people around me and I really want to thank
the bottom my heart
My friends, okay. Thank you. You are you keep you going on this show
Well Chanel, you know who knows there's no there's always up. Are you opted in by the way guys?
If you're not opted in for a
Possibility of a free membership if you click the gift button
It's green button at the top of the chat
It should say opt in to be eligible for free give to membership